A Guide to the Clifton A. Woodrum Papers, 1979-1999
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Numerical files, 1979-1999., Extent: 33.3 cu. ft. (74 boxes) (Box 1-74)
  - 59. Courts of Justice
    - [59.004-B] H.B. 1311 Controlled access highways penalties, 1991. (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - [59.004-C] H.B. 1678 and 1679 Family Court, 1993. (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - [59.004-C] H.B. 1678 and 1679 Family Court, 1993. (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - [59.004-D] Courts of Justice Committee reports, 1991-1992. (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - [59.005-A] Appellate Court Review, 1989. (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - [59.005-C] H.B. 1559 Release of liens, 1997. (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - [59.006-A] H.B. 151 Offers of settlement, 1990. (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - [59.006-B] Joint Subcommittee- Trial, Appeal, and Collateral Proceedings of Capital Cases HJR 402, 1993. (Box 70, Folder 1-10)
    - [59.006-B] Joint Subcommittee- Trial, Appeal, and Collateral Proceedings of Capital Cases HJR 402, 1993. (Box 71, Folder 1-4)
    - [59.006-D] S.B. 411 Whistle Blower Protection Act, 1994. (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
    - [59.007-A] H.B. 1309 Granting of continuances in civil cases, 1991. (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - [59.007-B] DUI meeting in Roanoke, 1993. (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - [59.008-A] H.B. 719 General district courts, 1992. (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - [59.008-B] H.B. 1077 Stalker bill 1992. (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - [59.009-A] H.B. 4 Posting streambeds, 1992. (Box 72, Folder 2-7)
  - 60. Supreme Court of Virginia
    - [60.001] Court of Appeals, 1988. (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - [60.002] Backlog in Supreme Court, 1989. (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - 61. Local Government Commission
    - [61.001] Local Government structures and relationships, 1989. (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - 62. District Courts
    - [62.001] Committee on District Courts- Reports, 1992. (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - [62.002] Committee on District Courts- Minutes, 1992-1993. (Box 73, Folder 5-6)
    - [62.002-A] Committee on District Courts- Meeting, 1991. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - [62.003] Central Criminal Records Exchange, 1991. (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - [62.004] John Dozier forms, 1994. (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - 63. Waste Management Dept.
    - [63.001] Yard waste composting at landfills, 1990. (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - [63.002] General correspondence, 1991. (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - [63.003] Recycling general correspondence, 1989-1992. (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - [63.003-B] Recycling batteries, 1991. (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - [63.004] Clivis septic system, 1991. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - [63.005] Solid Waste Act, 1999. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - 64. Claims
    - [64.002] H.B. 3 Claims, 1992. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - 65. Dept. of Personnel & Training (State Employees)
    - [65.001] Health Benefits Program for State Employees- Blue Cross Blue Shield- Key Advantage, 1992. (Box 74, Folder 5-7)
    - [65.001-A] Autologous bone marrow transplants, 1992. (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - 69. Appropriations Committee
    - [69.002] House Appropriations Committee Chairman's Newsletter, 1998-1999. (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - [69.003] Commonwealth Attorney's funding, 1998. (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - 70. Virginia Code Commission
    - [70.001] Virginia Code Commission, 1998. (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Series II: Legislation files, 1979-1999., Extent: 9.25 cu. ft. (21 boxes) (Box 75-95)
  This series was maintained in its original order and is organized by Legislation file numbers. The term 'Legislative' is misleading because all of the papers in this collection relate to legislation. Rather each folder was labeled 'Legis' followed by a number and it was gathered that Legis possibly stood for legislation.
  Includes correspondence, bills and resolutions, clippings, publications, reports and studies, and press releases on a variety of legislation and topics. Included is information on the appointment of court officials, banks and mortgages, unemployment, health insurance, child care, and the proposed merger of Roanoke city and county.
  Arranged numerically.
  - [Legis 2] Virginia Governmental Employee Association, 1979. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 4] Neighborhood Alliance, 1979-1980. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 6] Department of Welfare, 1979. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 7] Energy, 1979. (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 9] Emergency Medical Services, 1979. (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 11] H.B. 752 Repeal of tax on home heating bill, 1979. (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 12] Repeal of tax on non-prescription drugs, 1979. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 13] Senior citizens, 1979-1983. (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 14] Supreme Court of Virginia, 1979-1980. (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 14] Supreme Court of Virginia, 1979-1980. (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - [Legis 15] General District Court Judge, 1979-1980. (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 15] General District Court Judge, 1983. (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - [Legis 16] Initiative and Referendum, 1979. (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - [Legis 17] Residence of sheriffs, 1980. (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - [Legis 18] Truck weights, 1983. (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - [Legis 19] Census workers, 1980. (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - [Legis 20] Hunting and fishing licenses, 1979. (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - [Legis 20] Coal slurry pipeline, 1984-1985. (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 21] Wilkinson claim bill, 1974-1982. (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 24] General correspondence, 1984. (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 24] General correspondence, 1984. (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 24] General correspondence, 1985. (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 24] General correspondence, 1985. (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 24] General correspondence, 1985. (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 24] General correspondence, 1985. (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 24] General correspondence, 1986. (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 25] Virginia Retail Merchants Association, 1980. (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - [Legis 28] Commission on health care costs, 1979. (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 29] Report on standards of quality, 1979-1983. (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - [Legis 30] Legal services, 1983-1987. (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - [Legis 31] Health care, 1984-1985. (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 31] Curative statue, 1979. (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 34] Alleys, 1979-1980. (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 35] Virginia Taxpayers Association, 1980. (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 37] Virginia Farm Bureau Federation, 1979-1980. (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 41] ABC laws, 1980. (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 42] Gas tax, 1980. (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 42] Gas tax, 1980. (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 42] Gas tax, 1981-1982. (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 43] Emission standards, 1979-1980. (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - [Legis 44] Statue of limitations for products liability actions, 1979. (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 49] House Freshman Democratic Caucus, 1980. (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - [Legis 50] Uranium mining, 1982-1985. (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 53] The Center for Innovative Technology, 1983. (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 54] Budget, 1980. (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 55] S.B. 258 Sexual Assault Bill, 1980-1981. (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 56] Public school teachers, 1981. (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 57] Youth Haven II, 1983-1987. (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 58] Variable rate mortgages, 1980-1981. (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 59] Virginia Employment Commission, 1983. (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 60] Catawba Hospital, 1983. (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 61] Pesticide regulations City of Roanoke, 1980. (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 61] Bottle bill, 1986. (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - [Legis 62] Taxation of banks, 1979. (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - [Legis 63] Negligence in certain cases, 1980. (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - [Legis 64] S.B. 214 State Council of Higher Education, 1980. (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - [Legis 65] United ambulance service, 1980. (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - [Legis 66] S.B. 322 Beer and wine licenses, 1980. (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - [Legis 68] Roanoke Consumer Counseling Service, 1979-1980. (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 69] Co-sponsored legislation, 1980. (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 70] Insurance coverage for commonwealth, 1980. (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 72] Roll call votes, 1982-1983. (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 73] Heart, Lung, Hypertension Act, 1980. (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 74] Mill Mountain Zoo, 1980. (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 74] Commendations, 1979-1982. (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 74] Commendations, 1983. (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 74] Commendations, 1984. (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 75] H.B. 252, 1980. (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - [Legis 76] Bureau of Insurance, 1984-1986. (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 77] Roast-Delegate Tom Moss, 1984. (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - [Legis 78] Firefighters- Duane Dixon, 1984-1986. (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - [Legis 78] Joint Subcommittee Studying Virginia Unemployment Compensation Trust Fund, 1980. (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - [Legis 78] Joint Subcommittee Studying Virginia Unemployment Compensation Trust Fund, 1980. (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 78] Joint Subcommittee Studying Virginia Unemployment Compensation Trust Fund, 1980. (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 78] Joint Subcommittee Studying Virginia Unemployment Compensation Trust Fund, 1980. (Box 81, Folder 1-6)
  - [Legis 079] Comparable worth, 1984. (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 080] Virginia History Textbooks, 1981. (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 083] Classification of homes for adults, 1980. (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 084] Ethics panel, 1980. (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 085] Joint Subcommittee on Small Business, 1980. (Box 82, Folder 3-8)
  - [Legis 086] ABC License plates, 1980. (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 087] State Compensation Commission, 1980. (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 087] Mary Sue Terry- Attorney General for Virginia- Fundraiser, 1984-1985. (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 088] Appalachian Power Co., 1980. (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 089] State troopers, 1980. (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 090] Session Summaries, 1985. (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 090] Highway Dept., 1980. (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 092] Manhole safety, 1980. (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 093] Contributions, 1980. (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 095] Regulations, 1980. (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - [Legis 096] Council of Higher Education, 1980. (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 097] Petition to restore license, 1980. (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - [Legis 098] Workman's Compensation Claim- Denial of Occupational Disease, 1985. (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - [Legis 101] Piedmont Community College - J. M. Turner & Co., Inc., 1985-1986. (Box 83, Folder 14-15)
  - [Legis 102] Intermediate Court of Appeals, 1980. (Box 84, Folder 1-2)
  - [Legis 103] Merger of Blue Cross, Blue Shield, 1985-1986. (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 104] Fire Prevention Systems Incentive Subcommittee, 1985-1986. (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 104] H.B. 1042 Appointment of counsel for jail physicians, 1980. (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 105] Jefferson High School Project, 1985-1986. (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 105] Coal Technology Center, 1979. (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 106] Dram Shop Act, 1985. (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 106] Opinion of attorney general regarding Prudent Man Rule, 1980. (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 107] Electrical utilities, plan to deal with disasters, 1980. (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 108] H.B. 771 Curfew laws, 1980. (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 109] Security officers, 1980. (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 110] Legislative race contributions, 1979-1981. (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 112] Flood Damage Compensation Formula, 1985. (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 113] Radford University Telecommunications- University Communications Systems, 1986. (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 117] Southern Legislative Conference, 1987. (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 117] Sewage treatment plant of Roanoke city, 1980. (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 118] H.B. 1097 Estate accounting, 1980. (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 122] Radioactive waste disposal, 1980. (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 123] Virginia Freedom of Information Act, 1980. (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 126] Virginia Hospital Association, 1981. (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 126] Same Day Admission- Blue Cross, 1985-1986. (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 127] Roanoke city legislative file, 1981. (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - [Legis 130] H.B. 1095 Roanoke City Charter, 1981. (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 130] Industrial Development Authority Bonds- State Allocation Procedures, 1986. (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 134] Great Southwestern Caucus, 1981. (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - [Legis 136] Sponsorship of legislative bills, 1981. (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - [Legis 136] Indigents Medical Care, 1986-1987. (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - [Legis 140] Meetings, social events, etc., 1981. (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - [Legis 141] Purchase of foreign coal by electric utilities, 1985. (Box 86, Folder 1-3)
  - [Legis 141] H.B. 64 Handicapped parking, 1981. (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 142] H.B. 1643 Zoning bill, 1981. (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 144] H.B. 1077 Election timetable, 1981. (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 144] H.B. 767 Telephone public utilities subcommittee study, 1986. (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 145] State Water Control Board, 1981. (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 146] ABC Commission, differential in pay scales, 1981. (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 146] Conner, Aaron J. vs. Virginia Employment Commission, 1986. (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 147] Unauthorized practices of law- opinion of Attorney General, 1981. (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 147] Appointment of Conservator of Property for person aged 18-21, 1986. (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 151] Virginia Port authority Portsmouth facility, 1981. (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - [Legis 152] Appointment of Thomas Robertson Virginia Health Services Cost Review Commission, 1981. (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 152] Burial accounts, 1986. (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 153] Martin Luther King law, 1981. (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - [Legis 155] Mark K. Bonds, 1981. (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - [Legis 156] Commonwealth appointment of "agent of record", 1981. (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - [Legis 156] Death penalty, 1987. (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - [Legis 157] Elderly/handicapped unemployment compensation tax, 1981. (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - [Legis 157] Lifeguard of America, Inc., 1986. (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - [Legis 158] John D. Harvey memorial service, 1981. (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - [Legis 158] Insurance for court officers, 1986. (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - [Legis 159] POFF- Power of attorney, 1986. (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - [Legis 160] Almond Building, 1987. (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 163] Election, 1981. (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 163] Public Accounting Legislations, 1986. (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 164] Organizations, 1981. (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 165] ABC Commission winos, 1981. (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 165] Religious freedom, 1986. (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 166] Rate making SCC, 1981. (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 167] H.B. 1165 Gasoline dealers franchise fee, 1987. (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 168] Contributions, 1981. (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 169] Robb-Wilder conflict, 1986. (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 171] Federal Emergency Management Agency funds, 1982. (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - [Legis 173] Gruman Emergency Products plant, 1981. (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 173] Robert J. Wilkinson, Jr., 1986. (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 174] Sales tax home heating fuel, 1981. (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - [Legis 174] Equipment dealers, Franchise law exemption from liability, 1986. (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - [Legis 175] Codes for judges, 1981. (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 175] Va. Association of Community Agencies Awards, 1986. (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 177] Legislations, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 178] Gun control, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 179] H.B. 147 Massage parlors inspection warrants, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 181] H.B. 1012 Contingent powers of attorney, 1987. (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 182] Landlord/tenant laws, 1981. (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 184] H.B. 1021 Nonprofit debt counseling agencies, 1987. (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 187] H.B. 180 Fingerprinting, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 189] H.B. 65 Consumption of alcoholic beverages on school grounds, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 190] H.B. 63 City and County Treasurers, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - [Legis 191] S.B. 194 Increase in court cases, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 191A] H.B. 66 School board salaries, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - [Legis 192] H.B. 931, 932, 933 Income tax indexing, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - [Legis 192] H.B. 181 Unemployment compensation benefits to state and local governmental employees, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - [Legis 193] Sales price limitations, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - [Legis 195] Southern legislative conference 6th district, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - [Legis 196] Youth school day, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - [Legis 197] Mailings lists constituents, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - [Legis 198] Pro-ERA letters, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - [Legis 199] Anti-ERA letters, 1982. (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - [Legis 200] Labor letters, 1981. (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 201] H.B. 148, 245 Federal retire letter, 1982. (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 202] H.B 331 Parcel weight limit, 1982. (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 203] Teacher salary letters, 1982. (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 206] Release of liens, 1982. (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 207] Veto session, 1987. (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 209] Extension of water and sewer, 1981. (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 213] ACT Virginia, 1982. (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 214] DMV Services by sheriff, 1982. (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 216] Brambleton Ave. and Garst Mill Road intersection, Highway Dept., 1983. (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - [Legis 218] Campaign, 1982. (Box 89, Folder 11-12)
  - [Legis 221] Universal Communications Systems Inc., 1982. (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - [Legis 224] Ron Keith Adkins, MADD, and drunk driving charge against Chip,. (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - [Legis 225] H.B. 29 Relief for Frederick McIvor Shelor, 1983. (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - [Legis 228] City of Roanoke legislative program, 1983. (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - [Legis 230] Roanoke Post office conversion, 1982. (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 231] Campaign, 1983. (Box 90, Folder 2-4)
  - [Legis 235] Bradley properties, 1983. (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 236] H.B. 466- Community Action Act, 1982. (Box 90, Folder 6-8)
  - [Legis 237] H.B. 604 Architects and engineers, 1982. (Box 91, Folder 1-3)
  - [Legis 249] H.B 845- Contributions, 1983-1984. (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 256] Safeguard Business Systems 1983. (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 257] S.B. 105- Early Parole, 1983. (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 260] Legislative summaries, 1983. (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 261] Budget amendments, 1983. (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 264] Medicare Co-Insurance Reimbursement- Robertson, 1983-1984. (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 266] H.B. 329- Natural Death Act, 1983. (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - [Legis 273] Budget, 1984-1986. (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 274] Community Service Block Grants, 1983. (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - [Legis 277] Rutherfoord Insurance Co., 1985. (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 279] Nominations and recommendations, 1981. (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 279] Nominations and recommendations, 1982. (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 279] Nominations and recommendations, 1983. (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 279] Nominations and recommendations, 1984. (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 283] Regulatory Reform Advisory Board, 1983. (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 284] Lobbyists, 1983. (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 291] Sentencing, 1983. (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 297] City of Roanoke Legislative program, 1984. (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 299] Virginia Water and Sewer Authority, 1983. (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - [Legis 300] Lobbyists and spokesmen, 1984. (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - [Legis 301] Easter Seal Society, 1984. (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 302] Petroleum Products Franchise Act, 1983-1984. (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 305] H.B. 403- Garnishment statue, 1984. (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 306] H.B. 540- Land surveyors, 1984. (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 307] Professional Counselor Trainee, A. Wade Coffey, 1984. (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 308] Medical malpractice, 1985. (Box 93, Folder 6-8)
  - [Legis 308] Medical malpractice,. (Box 94, Folder 1-4)
  - [Legis 324] Proposed legislation, 1985. (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 327] Service of notice, 1984. (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 334] Gubernatorial campaign, Baliles, 1985. (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - [Legis 335] Attorney General opinion on Marvin Arrington, 1984. (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - [Legis 336] H.B. 698- Cigarette Sales Below Wholesale Cost Act penalty, 1984. (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - [Legis 337] Lobbyists, 1985. (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - [Legis 341] S.B. 356-Child Care Bill, 1984. (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - [Legis 342] Licensing, Limitation on social workers, 1984. (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - [Legis 343] Ronald McDonald House, Tax exemption, 1984-1985. (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - [Legis 344] Virginia Synod Lutheran Home,. (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - [Legis 345] City of Roanoke Legislative Program, 1985. (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - [Legis 349] H.B. 817- Disabilities Act, 1985. (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - [Legis 361] Proposed legislation, 1985. (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Series III: Dated files, 1979-1999., Extent: 17.55 cu. ft. (39 boxes) (Box 96-123)
  This series was maintained in its original order and arranged chronologically by year. Includes legislative and campaign files, correspondence, Virginia House and Senate bills, budgets, clippings, press releases, and studies. The campaign files include clippings, staff lists, contribution lists, legislative and voting records, and campaign projects and events. The legislative files include correspondence, budgets, and bills.
  Includes information on VEPCO's proposed Coal Slurry Pipeline through Virginia; medical malpractice laws; Democratic Party of Virginia; constituent correspondence; Birth Related- Neurological Injury Compensation Fund; Roanoke Higher Education Center; and letters of recommendation.
  Arranged chronologically into 8 subseries.
  - Subseries 1. 1979, Extent: 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
    - Campaign and expenditure files, 1979. (Box 96-97)
  - Subseries 2. 1980-1994, Extent: 3.15 cu. ft. (7 boxes)
    - 1980, Correspondence. (Box 98, Folder 1-8)
    - 1980, Labor and Commerce Committee. (Box 98, Folder 9-10)
    - 1980-1982, Lobbyists. (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - 1980, Neighborhood Assistance Act. (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - 1980, Norfolk and Western. (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - 1980, Shelor vs. Roanoke. (Box 98, Folder 14-15)
    - 1980, Virginia Plan for Community Education. (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - 1980, [H.B. 30] Budget. (Box 98, Folder 17-19)
    - 1980, [H.B. 57] Roanoke Charter. (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - 1981, Almanac of Virginia Politics. (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - 1981, Campaign. (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - 1981, Correspondence. (Box 99, Folder 3-10)
    - 1981, Democratic Convention. (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - 1981, Buzz Emick election. (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - 1981, Military leave. (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - 1981, Resources for Teaching Virginia Government. (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - 1981, Robb Gubernatorial race. (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - 1981, Roll call. (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - 1981, WVWR. (Box 99, Folder 17-18)
    - 1981, [H.B. 1145] Telecommunications. (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - 1982, Board of Housing and Community Development. (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - 1982, Campaign manual. (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - 1982, Correspondence. (Box 100, Folder 3-7)
    - 1982-1983, Directory of Community Services. (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - 1982, Legislative weekend, Roanoke. (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - 1982, Medical issues. (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - 1982, [H.B. 465] Bill of relief. (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - 1982, [H.B. 467] Fuel tax. (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - 1982, [H.B 468] Bill of relief. (Box 100, Folder 13)